All right, great. We're doing a lot of funding right,
非常好，我们已经做了很多注资的工作了，对吧？
and we keep funding our contract with more and more Ethan,
并且我们在不断地为我们的合约注入更多的以太币资金
we keep adding more and more stuff,
我们还在不断的添加越来越多的内容
we probably want a button to keep track of how much is actually in here.
我们还希望能有一个按钮，可以追踪到这里实际上已经有多少资金了
So let's just add a really simple balance button.
所以让我们来添加一个简单的“余额”("balance")按钮
And let me actually just move this down to the bottom here, much better.
让我来把它移动到底部这里，好看多了
So we'll say button, id equals balance button.
我们来写下 ``
We'll call it get balance.
我们给它命名为 `getBalance`
Now we have a get balanced button.
现在我们就有了一个 "getBalance" 按钮
And it's not going to do anything because we don't have a get balanced function.
它还没有任何作用，因为我们还没有用于获取余额的函数
So let's go back to our index.js. And we'll create a get bounced function
所以回到我们的 "index.js"，我们来创建一个用于获取余额的函数
async function get bounce.
`async function getBalance(){}`
And we'll just do what we've been doing so far.
我们要做的就是迄今为止我们一直在做的事
If type of window dot Aetherium does not equal, undefined,
`if(typeof window.ethereum != "undefined")`
then we're going to do const provider equals new ethers, ethers, dot providers dot web three provider of window, that Aetherium
接着执行 `const provider = new ethers.providers.Web3Provider(window.ethereum)`
then will do const balance equals awaits provider dot get balance, contract address,
然后是 `const balance = await provider.getBalance(contractAddress)`
which again, we're importing way up at the top,
再次提醒，我们已经在顶部导入了它们
and then we'll just do console dot log ethers dot utils dot format, ether, bounce
然后我们直接运行 `console.log(ethers.utils.formatEther(balance))`
this format ether function ethers utils, which you can find in the documentation
这个 "formatEther" 是 "ethers.utils" 中的函数，你可以在文档中找到它
to make reading ethers, formatted numbers much easier to read.
它的作用是格式化 ethers 输出的数字使其更加易读
Then same as what we've been doing before,
然后，就和我们之前做的一样
we're going to go up, we're going to copy this fun button line,
翻到上面，复制 "fundButton" 这一行
paste it will say balance button equals document dot get element by ID,
粘贴一下，然后改成 `balanceButton = document.getElementById()`
balance button.
"balanceButton"
And then we'll say balance button on click equals get balance,
接着我们说 `balanceButton.onclick = getBalance`
we're gonna come back to our front end, we'll do a quick refresh, we'll do get balance.
我们回到前端，快速刷新一下，点击 "getBalance"
And now we can see the balance in the console,
现在我们就可以在“控制台”("Console")中看到余额了
we can fund with more like 1.8,
我们还可以注入更多资金，比如 1.8
we'll hit fund metamath pops up, we'll go ahead and confirm
点击 "Fund"，MetaMask 弹了出来，继续点击“确认”("Confirm")
mining completed done,
"Mining", "Completed", "Done!"
we hit get balanced, and now we're at 3.8. Fantastic.
再次点击 "getBalance"，现在我们得到了 3.8，太棒了！